{
    "id": "7afc6963d1664aaf84f587d53672fa3f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Your sister is ………………… nuisance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quite a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………. annoyed to find him in her room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ……………… cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very cold – you ……………….. take a coat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have better",
                "had better"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………. imaginative.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "not very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. a painter are you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How much",
                "How much of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I think she is ………………… a fool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a bit",
                "a bit of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………… informal get-together than a meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more a",
                "more of",
                "more of an"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You have been ………………..!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such help",
                "such a help!"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Stop talking ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such nonsense",
                "such a nonsense"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}